<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="dialog_title_first_start">First Start</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_delete_recipe_collection">Deleting Recipe Collection</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_ask_refactor">Overriding First Day Of The Week</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_begin_refactor">Begin Refactor</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_refactoring">Refactoring Data</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_data_corruption">Potential Data Corruption</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_delete_ingredient">Delete Ingredient</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_delete_recipe">Delete Recipe</string>

    <string name="dialog_text_first_start_intro">
        It seems this is the first time you open this app. You can choose between one of the two
        following options for your first install (not choosing will have the same effect as
        choosing "Fresh Start").\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="dialog_text_first_start_fresh_start">Fresh Start:</string>
    <string name="dialog_text_first_start_fs_explain">
        (If you have already used this app in the past) Start with a completely empty app so that
        you can directly add all and only your ingredients, recipes and meals.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="dialog_text_first_start_basic_template">Basic Template:</string>
    <string name="dialog_text_first_start_bt_explain">
        (Suggested) Create a basic template that can be manually modified or deleted later. This
        way you\'ll have a rough idea of what the app should look like and how each functionality
        works.
    </string>
    <string name="dialog_text_recipes_type_name">Recipes Type Name:</string>
    <string name="dialog_text_recipes_type_file_name">File Name:</string>
    <string name="dialog_text_delete_recipe_collection">
        Do you really want to delete this recipe collection? All the relative data will be lost.
    </string>
    <string name="dialog_text_ask_refactor">
        You\'re about to change the first day of your weekly plans. If you have some already saved
        weeks, the app will have to refactor that data and "shift" it so that they start with the
        new first day of the week. By doing so, some garbage-filler data (empty meals) will be
        created and some data might be lost (you\'ll be informed about what (if any) specific data
        will be lost before proceeding and you\'ll be asked again to confirm later on)
        \n\nDo you want to proceed?
    </string>
    <string name="dialog_text_begin_refactor">Checking for potential data corruption…</string>
    <string name="dialog_text_refactoring">Refactoring… Do not close this app.</string>
    <string name="dialog_text_data_corruption">
        It looks like there are some pairs of consecutive weeks where the first week has a Day
        Format (Daily Meals) different to the second week\'s. This makes it unable for the app to
        refactor those two weeks and will end up in losing data relative to half of one of those
        two weeks. Do you want to change the first day of the week and refactor anyway?
        \n\nList of problematic pairs (any week not included in this list won\'t go corrupt and
        will be saved just fine):\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="dialog_text_delete_ingredient">Are you sure you want to delete this ingredient?</string>
    <string name="dialog_text_delete_recipe">Are you sure you want to delete this recipe?</string>

    <string name="dialog_button_first_start_fresh_start">Fresh\nStart</string>
    <string name="dialog_button_first_start_basic_template">Basic\nTemplate</string>
    <string name="dialog_button_data_corruption_yes">YES\n(Refactor)</string>
    <string name="dialog_button_data_corruption_no">NO\n(Do Nothing)</string>
</resources>